Sade Sirén

20.12.2017

Information



Aurorankatu 26 B 34, 20320 Turku 0505752584

siren.sade@gmail.com / sade.siren@edu.turkuamk.fi

LinkedIN profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sade-sir%C3%A9n/

Art Portfolio: https://www.artstation.com/fyrd8th
Project Portfolio: https://sadesirn.portfoliobox.net/

GitHub: https://github.com/Fyrd8th

OBJECTIVE

My goal is to become a renowned game producer and software developer. I plan to produce a minimum of four mobile games to be globally released within a five-year period with my team at Vainary ay as well as add more public projects into my GitHub.

EDUCATION

Turku University of Applied Sciences

Graduated: 12/2018

Bachelor of Engineering, Information and Communications Technology

University of Turku

Graduated: 05/2008
Master of Social Sciences

EXPERIENCE

Collection specialist | Lindorff Oy

8/2010 - Present

Customer service (inbound, outbound, written) for all major stakeholders throughout the service portfolio. Served as a trainer for junior personnel.

Customer Advisor | Onecapital Oy

11/2009 - 07/2010

Collection service throughout the portfolio.

Office worker | Euronic Oy

11/2008 - 10/2009

Credit service, bank transfers, customer service.

Shop manager | Sonera Piste Oy

05/2008 - 09/2008

Sales, managing the team and workspace.

Trainee | Department of Philosophy, University of Turku

05/2007 - 08/2007

Independent research, assisting research and editing.

Sales | Sonerapiste Oy

12/2006 - 05/2007

Customer service, sales.

Interviewer | Berent Oy

08/2006 - 10/2006

Phone interviews for company image research.

Project Interviewer | Corporate Image Oy

09/2003 - 08/2006

Phone interviews for company image research, checking research findings.

Data input | Orion Pharma Oy

06/2003 - 06/2003 and 02/2005 - 02/2005

Archiving, documenting.

Sales | Järvenkylän mansikkafarmi

06/2003 - 08/2006, 06/2004 - 08/2004 and 06/2005 - 08/2005 Selling seasonal products.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

Unity coding with C#

Photography

Game design

Storytelling

COOPERATION

I have been a team manager for several game projects, and I can work easily both as a member of a close-knit group or as an independent worker from off-site. I am known as a reliable person who produces quality quickly.

LEADERSHIP

I have served as president and board member in two university student associations at University of Turku.

I have lead teams as a project manager on several game development projects that can be found in my portfolio.

REFERENCES

Tiina Järvinen, Lindorff Oy

Group manager, no contact information (deceased)

Tomi Alieskola, Sonera Piste Oy

Region manager, 0400-780962, tomi.ali-eskola@sonerapiste.fi

Sari Myllyviita, Orion Pharma Oy

QA manager, 050-4297485, sari.myllyviita@orionpharma.com